Finding Aid for Sam Sturgis Photograph collection
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Ann Arbor
  - AA 201 - AA 249
    - Train wreck north of Ann Arbor Railroad depot in 1910 including children observing at First St. between William and Liberty Sts. 1910, AA 210 --; copy neg. (Box 1)
    - View of UM Campus., AA 211 --; copy neg. na 15,541 (Box 1)
    - University Hall on UM campus., AA 212 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - View of UM campus., AA 213 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Huron St. from Main St. c. 1878 taken from stereo card. 1878, AA 214 --; [5x7] (Box 1)
    - View of Main St. northeast from Liberty St. from stereo card during the 1880s. circa 1880, AA 215 --; copy neg. only. [5x7] No print. (Box 1)
    - View of Main St. northwest from Liberty St. c. 1870. circa 1870, AA 216 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Panoramic view northeast from Courthouse., AA 217 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
      (Duplicate print taken from stereo card. Source: Ray Hutzel.)
    - View of Main St. northwest from Washington St. sometime between 1868 and 1874. circa 1870, AA 218 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
      (Source: L. Eberbach.)
    - Drake's Saloon and Jacob Haller's Jewelry c. 1875 on East Huron St. across from the Courthouse. circa 1875, AA 219 --; copy neg. (Box 1)
      (Source: L. Eberbach. na 13,546)
    - Eberbach Hardware in 1892 or 1895 on East Washington and Main Sts. circa 1895, AA 220 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - View of North University Ave. from State St. in 1910. 1910, AA 221.1 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Postal Telegraph Office in 1888. 1888, AA 221.2 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Bach and Abel Store during the 1880s at Main and Liberty Sts. circa 1880, AA 221.3 --; copy neg. (Box 1)
      (Source: MHC. na 1,893/na 947)
    - 200 block of East Huron St. across from the Ann Arbor Fire Department c. 1870. circa 1870, AA 221.4 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Broadway near Wall St., AA 221.5 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - State St. north of William St. in 1892. 1892, AA 221.6 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Paul J. Allured at the Postal Telegraph Union or Postal Telegraph Cable Co., located in Cornwell Building, then called Hamilton Block on Huron St. and North Fourth Ave. c. 1895 circa 1895, AA 221.7 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
      [See also AA-313]
    - Postal Telegraph Union Office (Postal Telegraph Cable Co.)located in Cornwell Building, then called Hamilton Block on Huron St. and N. Fourth Ave. c. 1895 circa 1895, AA 221.8 --; copy neg. (Box 1)
      (Source: MHC. na 13,260)
      [See also AA-313.]
    - Ann Arbor High School, 1856-79., AA 221.9 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Checker players playing by gaslight in the Postal Telegraph Union Office in 1888. 1888, AA 221.10 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Wagon loaded with barrels in 1880 for delivery to Binder's Saloon at 6 West Liberty St. 1880, AA 221.11 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Looking north on State St. from University Hall between 1863 and 1876. circa 1870, AA 221.12 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Main St. in Ann Arbor., AA 221.13 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Looking east on North University Ave. from State St., AA 221.14 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Goodyear and St. James Store between 1888 and 1895 at Main and Liberty Sts. circa 1890, AA 221.15 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Two residences., AA 221.16 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Michigan Central Railroad depot., AA 221.17 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Looking south on State St. from North University Ave c. 1920 with new Nickels Arcade on right. circa 1920, AA 221.18 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Methodist Episcopal Church at State and Washington Sts., AA 221.19 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Observatory St. north from Geddes Road during the early 1920s with cemetery at right. circa 1920, AA 221.20 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Argo Mills in Ann Arbor's Lower Town., AA 221.21 --; copy neg. (Box 1)
      (Source: MHC. Argo Mills burned in 1900. na 15,542)
    - Mack and Company store fire on 15 May 1899 at 1:30 pm on Main St. (Ann Arbor's first large department store.) 1899, AA 221.22 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Mack and Company store fire on 15 May 1899 at 1:30 pm on Main St. (Ann Arbor's first large department store.) 1899, AA 221.23 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Mack and Company store fire on 15 May 1899 at 1:30 pm on Main St. (Ann Arbor's first large department store.) 1899, AA 221.24 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - View of the north side of West Huron St. at Ninth St. including windmill., AA 221.25 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
      (Source: MHC. Photographer: Lyndon.)
    - Toledo and Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge over Huron River., AA 221.26 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - UM boathouse and canoes on Huron River., AA 221.27 --; copy neg. (Box 1)
      (Source: MHC. na 15,543)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor from-the northwest c. 1885 with UM at left and Courthouse at right. circa 1885, AA 221.28 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - St. Thomas Parochial School on Elizabeth St., AA 221.29 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Old Ann Arbor High School, orig. built 1895, burned 1904 and rebuilt 1908. At E. Washington and Thayer Sts., AA 221.30 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Former Ann Arbor High School, now UM Frieze Building., AA 221.31 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - State St. and South University Ave., the southwest corner of campus, in 1875. Methodist Episcopal Church in distance. circa 1875, AA 221.32 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - New York and Michigan Central Railroads depot between circa 1896-1898. 1900, AA 221.33 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Washtenaw Hotel at 13 Broadway c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 221.34 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
    - Michigan Central Railroad depot., AA 221.35 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 1)
      (Source; MHC.)
    - View of Liberty and Main Sts. from the St. James Company Store in 1875. Christian Schmid's lumberyard seen on the Fifth Ave. corner is present site of the Federal Building. 1875, AA 221.36 --; copy neg. (Box 1)
    - Junius Beal residence during 1890s, present site of the Ann Arbor Public Library. Two women on porch. Two men including J. Beal with large-wheel bicycle. (Corner of Fifth Ave. and William St.) circa 1890, AA 222 --; copy neg. [5x7] No print. (Box 2)
      (Source: Loretta Edwards.)
    - Junius Beal residence during the 1890s at corner of Fifth Ave. and William St. present site of the Ann Arbor Public Library. circa 1890, AA 223 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Dr. Chase Book Bindery and Printing House at Main and Ann Sts. around 1880. circa 1880, AA 224 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Post Office at the northeast corner of Main and Ann Sts., AA 225 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - State St. north of William St. in 1907. 1907, AA 226.1 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - University of Michigan County Fair on May 1 and 2, 1908. Photo taken from postcard promotion. 1908, AA 226.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - UM football Coach Yost buying Liberty Bond in 1917 (with Troop 4 Boy Scouts?). 1917, AA 227 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Published. Source: Hudson Norton. na 13,887)
    - South University Ave. looking west from East University Ave. including Halls Greenhouse. Photo from first of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.1 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - South University Ave. looking west from East University Ave. Photo taken from first of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.2 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - UM diagonal looking northwest from East University Ave. Photo taken from first of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.3 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - East University Ave. looking north from South University Ave. Photo taken from first of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.4 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - South University Ave. possibly with Old Engineering Building on north side of street. Photo taken from second of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.5 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - North side of South University Ave. with Old Engineering Building. Photo taken from second of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.6 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - North side of South University looking toward East University Ave. Photo taken from second of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.7 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - North side of South University looking east toward East University Ave. Photo taken from third of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.8 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Looking south from South University and East University Ave. Photo taken from third of four sets of surveying photographs, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.9 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Looking south toward South University Ave. and Hall's Greenhouse. Photo taken from third of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.10 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Looking southwest toward South University and Hall's residence. Photo taken from third of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.11 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
      (Source; MHC)
    - Building on north side of South University Ave. Photo from third of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.12 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Looking south toward East University Ave. Photo from fourth of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.13 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Looking southwest from East University Ave. Photo from fourth of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.14 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Looking west across East University toward campus. Photo from fourth of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.15 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Looking northwest across East University Ave. toward campus. Photo from fourth of four sets of surveying photos, possibly cyanotypes., AA 228.16 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Horse-drawn hook and ladder no. 2, Ann Arbor Fire Department on 17 September 1906. 1906, AA 229A --; [5x7] (Box 2)
      (Source: Paul Seitz, Dexter. Photographer: Lyndon.)
    - Horse-drawn hose co. no. 3, Engine House no. 1, Ann Arbor Fire Department, 17 September 1906. 1906, AA 229B --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Horse-drawn hose co. no. 1, Engine House no. 1, Ann Arbor Fire Department, 17 September 1906. 1906, AA 229C --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - View looking east up William St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.1 --; copy neg. and no print. (Box 2)
    - View looking west down Huron St. from State St. intersection in 1968. 1968, AA 230.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source and photographer: Sturgis.)
    - View looking west on North University Ave. toward State St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.3 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking north on Glen Ave. toward Catherine St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.4 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking south on State St. from Liberty St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.5 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking north on State St. from William St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.6 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking west on North University Ave. and State St. 1968, AA 230.7 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking south on State St. from near Liberty St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.8 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking southwest on Pontiac Trail from Longshore in 1568. 1968, AA 230.9 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking east on North University Ave. from State St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.10 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking north on Main St. from Sunset Ave. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.11 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking north on Main St. from Liberty St. in 1968. 1968, AA 230.12 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor looking southwest from Cedar Bend Drive in 1968. 1968, AA 230.13 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking west down Penn Central Railroad tracks at the Ann Arbor Railroad depot in 1968. 1968, AA 230.14 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Geddes Road bridge over the Huron River in 1968. 1968, AA 230.15 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Assorted views of Ann Arbor and North Campus., AA 230.16-AA 230.32 -- (Box 2)
    - View looking east on North University Ave. from State St. in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.1 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking east on North University Ave. from State St. in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking north on State St. at North University Ave. in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.3 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking south on State St. from North University Ave. in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.4 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view northeast from old St. Josephs Hospital parking lot in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.5 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.6 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - View looking northeast from Broadway and Broadway Bridge in 1968. 1968, AA 231.7 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Depot St. looking southwest from Broadway Bridge in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.8 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Observatory Street looking north from Geddes Road in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.9 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View looking northeast from old St. Josephs Hospital parking lot in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.10 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Wall St. looking north to Broadway from Canal St. in April 1968. 1968, AA 231.11 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor views unnumbered and unprinted in 1968. 1968, AA 231.12 --; copy negs. No prints. (Box 2)
    - Assorted views of Ann Arbor., AA 231.13-AA 231.20 -- (Box 2)
    - Three of fifty-three bells from England to be placed in the Baird Memorial Tower., AA 232.1 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: RE Schlupe)
    - First highway bus from Ann Arbor to Detroit., AA 232.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Schlupe.)
    - UM old storehouse on Forest Ave. 1923 Reo truck and Tom Knight and Alex Schlupe included in photo. circa 1925, AA 232.3 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: RE Schlupe.)
    - RC Barney Marble and Granite Works., AA 232.4 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Possibly UM's first truck, a Pierce Arrow. Photo includes a group of men., AA 232.5 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: RE Schlupe. Photographer: Alex Schlupe.)
    - Possibly UM's first truck., AA 232.6 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: RE Schlupe. Photographer: Tom Knight.)
    - Ann Arbor Ice House on Huron River east of Whitmore Lake Bridge. North Main St. next to Argo Pond., AA 232.7 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
      [See also AA 274.1]
    - Corner of West Liberty and Ashley Sts., Kurtz Building at 120 W. Liberty St. c. 1898. 1898, AA 232.8 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Exterior of the Preketis family's Sugar Bowl restaurant at 109 South Main St., AA 232.9 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of the Farmers and Mechanics Bank after the streetcar accident in 1910. 1910, AA 232.10A --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of the Farmers and Mechanics Bank after the streetcar accident in 1910. 1910, AA 232.10B --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of the Farmers and Mechanics Bank after the streetcar accident in 1910. 1910, AA 232.10C --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of the Farmer and Mechanics Bank after the streetcar accident in 1910. 1910, AA 232.10D --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of the accident on the Ann Arbor Railroad., AA 233.1A --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of the accident on the Ann Arbor Railroad., AA 233.1B --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Exterior of the old Ann Arbor Post Office at northeast corner of Main and Ann Sts., AA 233.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of State St. side of UM campus including horse and carriages., AA 234 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Clark.)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.1 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.2 --; copy neg. only. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.3 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.4 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.5 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.6 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.7 --; copy neg. only. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.8 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.9 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.10 --; copy neg. only. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.11 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.12 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.13 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.14 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.15 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.16 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.17 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 23S.18 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968 1968, AA 235.19 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.20 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.21 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.22 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.23 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Street view of Ann Arbor Art Fair in 1968. 1968, AA 235.24 --; copy neg. No print. (Box 2)
    - Argo Mills after fire in 1900. 1900, AA 236.1 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Erwin J. Otis.)
    - Collapse of Ann Arbor Railroad bridge over the Huron River., AA 236.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Collapse of Ann Arbor Railroad bridge including piled-up cargo., AA 236.3 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - St. Thomas Catholic Church c. 1903. 1903, AA 237 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Bill Tuomy Estate.)
    - William Jennings Bryan at Washtenaw County Courthouse., AA 238 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Haller.)
    - Aerial view of Washtenaw Gas Company on Broadway and Michigan Central Railroad depot in 1929. 1929, AA 239A --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
      (Source: Milton Kemnetz.)
    - View of Washtenaw Gas Company on Broadway., AA 239B --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - Bethlehem United Church in 1881 with group of men, women and children in front. Built by early German settlers in 1833 on present site of Bethlehem Cemetery on Jackson Road. 1881, AA 240 --; copy neg. [5x7] (Box 2)
    - View of southeast corner of Main and Washington Sts. in January 1950. 1950, AA 241.1 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: AA News/Eck Stanger.)
    - County Building at corner of Huron St. and Fourth Ave. in October 1952. 1952, AA 241.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Eck Stanger/AA News)
    - Fischer's Hardware located in the Weinmann Block at East Washington St. and South Fifth Ave. in 1952. 1952, AA 241.3 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Eck Stanger/AA News.)
    - Northwest corner of Main and Huron Sts. in 1952. 1952, AA 241.4 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Main and Huron Sts. in March 1951. 1951, AA 241.5 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Eck Stanger/ Ann Arbor News.)
    - View of Ann Arbor Railroad Bridge in 1952 with Gas Company in background. 1952, AA 241.6 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: Eck Stanger/Ann Arbor News.)
    - The Majestic Theater on Maynard St. South of Liberty St. in 1948-49. 1948, AA 241.7 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Footbridge at the corner of Broadway and Swift St. in 1917. 1917, AA 242 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Published. Source: Mrs. MD Smith.)
    - Residence of Thomas McIntyre Cooley on State St. and South University Ave., present site of Michigan Union, sometime after 1875. circa 1880, AA 243 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Scenic view of Lower Town from Catholic Church on North State St. in 1922. 1922, AA 244.1 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Washington Block of businesses at Washington St. and Fourth Ave. about 1907. 1907, AA 244.2 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Wall St. Bridge collapsed on 6 August 1909. 1909, AA 244.3 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: MHC. Photographer: Benham.)
    - Corner of Huron and Main Sts. c. 1900(?). circa 1900, AA 244.4 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Main St., AA 244.5 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Second Michigan Central RR bridge east of Ann Arbor. Photo taken 24 April 1897. 1897, AA 244.6 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Looking up-river from second Michigan Central RR bridge in 1897. 1897, AA 244.7 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - View of Main St., AA 244.8 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Michigan Central Railroad depot., AA 244.9 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department engine house at Huron St. and Fifth Ave., AA 244.10 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - The Glazier Building, Ann Arbor's first multi-storied building, under construction in 1906 at North Main St. 1906, AA 244.11 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - South University Ave. looking west from East University Ave., AA 244.12 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Two men with bicycles., AA 244.13 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Packard St. streetcar, with motorman Jim Love and conductor Marion Darling., AA 244.14 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor from the northwest in 1876. 1876, AA 244.15 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
      (Source: MHC. na 957)
    - Washtenaw Hotel at 13 Broadway c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 244.16 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor from the northwest in 1876 with man in foreground. 1876, AA 244.17 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Gregory House at the northwest corner of Main and Huron Sts., later Municipal Court Building c. 1868. 1868, AA 244.18 -- (Box 2)
      (Source: MHC. Warren Photo.)
    - Sixth grade sewing class at Perry School in February 1911 with teacher Miss Holen(?). African-American girl in photo. 1911, AA 244.19 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Huron St. looking east from Main St., AA 244.20 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Huron St. looking east from Main St., AA 244.21 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Herrick and Bohnet Store at 208 North Fourth Ave. Photo taken on 1 July 1908. 1908, AA 244.22 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Ann Arbor Fire Department engine house at Huron St. and Fifth Ave., AA 244.10 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - The Glazier Building, Ann Arbor's first multi-storied building, under construction in 1906 at North Main St. 1906, AA 244.11 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - South University Ave. looking west from East University Ave., AA 244.12 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Two men with bicycles., AA 244.13 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Packard St. streetcar, with motorman Jim Love and conductor Marion Darling., AA 244.14 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor from the northwest in 1876. 1876, AA 244.15 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Washtenaw Hotel at 13 Broadway c. 1910. circa 1910, AA 244.16 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Panoramic view of Ann Arbor from the northwest in 1876 with man in foreground. 1876, AA 244.17 --; copy neg. (Box 2)
    - Gregory House at the northwest corner of Main and Huron Sts., later Municipal Court Building c. 1868. 1868, AA 244.18 -- (Box 2)